Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- National APA Conference, "Transportation Needs Identification", 2000; 0174 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Integrative Comprehensive Planning", 2000; 0175 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Recreating the Suburban Strip", 2000; 0176 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Empowerment Zones in the Black Community", 2000; 0177 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Aesthetics of Open Space Planning", 2000; 0178 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Development and Annexation Agreements", 2000; 0179 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Growing Inward", 2000; 0180 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Sex and the City", 2000; 0181 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Top Ten Landmarks and Pioneers", 2000; 0182 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Parking Impacts on Downtowns", 2000; 0183 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Environment Performance Standards", 2000; 0184 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Model Environmental Planning", 2000; 0185 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Bikeways and Tea-21", 2000; 0186 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Impact on Growth Management", 2000; 0187 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "New York City Zoning", 2000; 0188 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Planning Law", 2000; 0189 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Redeveloping Failed Shopping Malls", 2000; 0190 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Neighborhoods and Brownfields", 2000; 0191 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "International Perspectives on teh Land Use/Transportation Connection", 2000; 0192 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Preparing for a Career in Planning", 2000; 0193 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Does Downtown Reinvestment Work?", 2000; 0194 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Dealing with National Drugstores", 2000; 0195 (Box 89)
- American Planning Association Annual Meeting - Book 1, 1987 (Box 88, Folder APA-701 - APA-716)
- American Planning Association Annual Meeting - Book 2, 1987 (Box 88, Folder APA-717 - APA-731)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, GA - Book 3, 1989 (Box 88, Folder APA-916 - APA-930)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, GA - Book 4 (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 88, Folder APA-931 - APA-947)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, GA - Book 4 (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 88, Folder APA-948 - APA-959)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, GA - Book 5, 1989 (Box 88, Folder APA-960 - APA-975)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, GA - Book 6, 1989 (Box 88 Series, Folder APA-976 - APA-987)
- APA Awards Jury Meeting, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Award Nomination - Fall Creek Place, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- "Implementation" Award Submissions, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Distinguished Service Award - Chris McGetrick, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Student Planner - Margaret Ounsworth, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Nomination - "Destination 2030", 2003 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Leadership Award Nomination - Tom Mullen, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Paul Daridoff Award, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Nomination for Leadership Award - David Wallace, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- APA Award for Special Community Initiative - Melbourne, FL, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Public Education Award - League of Women Voters Buffalo/Niagara, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Award Submission - Farmersville, California, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Planning Magazine, Call for Entries, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- "Reading the Land," - Massachusetts Heritage Landscapes, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Leadership Award Application - Ruth Ann Minner, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Leadership Award - Andrea Mead Lawrence, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Special Community Initiative Nomination - "City of Paducan Lower Town", 2004 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Award Submission - "Urban Design Framework," Washington, D.C., 2004 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Leadership Award Nominee - Barbara Lukermann, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Award Submission - "Presidio Trust Management Plan", 2004 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- Award Application - "Chicago Metropolis 2020", 2004 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Award Nomination - "Old York Village", 2004 (Box 110, Folder 22)
- Distinguished Service Nomination - Connie B. Cooper, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 23)
- Current Topic Award Nomination - "Chambers Creek", 2004 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- APA Applications, Magazines, call for entries, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 25)
- Karen B. Smith Chapter Awards, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- APA Award Nomination - Ron Stewart, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 27)
- Award Submission - "Women Resident Activists at Wentworth Gardens", 2005 (Box 110, Folder 28)
- Distinguished Leadership Award, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Outstanding Planning Award - "Queen City Hub," Buffalo, NY, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 30)
- Current Topic Award - "The National Capital Urban Design and Security Plan", 2005 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- Daniel Burnham Award - Santa Monica Mountains Conservancy, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 32)
- National Women in Planning Award Nomination - Margarita Piel McCoy, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 33)
- Outstanding Planning Award Submission - "Extending the Vision for South Broad Street," Philadelphia, PA, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 34)
- Does Your Town Need A Planner?;How to Design a Kid's Charette; Facilitator's Workshop, 1984-1997 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Video Training: The Best of Planning For Zoning Administrator, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Video Training Package: Effectiveness, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Community Visioning, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Video Training: Costs of Sprawl, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Design Review: From Historic Preservation to Site Plans, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Community "X" Gaming Kit, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Video Training Package: Electronic Town Meetings, Undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Using Scientific Information For Better Planning, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Protecting National Wetlands, Florida's Wildlife habitat Conservation System, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Planning for Wildlife in Cities/Suburbs, Oak Harbor, WA Ordinance #977, 1978-1996 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- Wetlands Mitigation Banking, Managing Maryland's Growth, 1992-1996 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- APA: Reinventing the Strip Part 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- APA: Reinventing the Strip Part 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 14)
- APA: Responding To and Planning For Telecommunications, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 15)
- Telecommunications - General Readings, 1995-1997 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- APA: City Planning and Management News, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 17)
- APA: Economic Development, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 18)
- APA: Environmental, Natural Resources and Energy, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 19)
- APA: Federal Installation Planners, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 20)
- APA: Housing and Human Services, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- APA: Information Technology, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 22)
- APA: Intergovernmental Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 23)
- APA: International Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 24)
- APA: Planning and Law, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 25)
- APA: Planning and the Black Community, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 26)
- APA: Planning and Women, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 27)
- APA: Private Practice, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 28)
- APA: Resorts and Tourism, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 29)
- APA: Small Town and Rural Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 30)
- APA: Transportation Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 31)
- APA: Urban Design and Preservation Quarterly, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 32)
- APA: The New Planner, 1993-1996 (Box 114, Folder 33)
- APA: The Student Planner, 1984-1992 (Box 114, Folder 34)
- APA: Student Representative Council Continental Comments, Newsletter, 1980-1984 (Box 114, Folder 35)
- Audio Conference Program: Legal Foundation for Planning Commission and Zoning Board of Appeals, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 36)
- Audio Conference Program: Innovative Controls for Land Use Regulation, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 37)
- Audio Conference Program: Updating the Zoning Ordinance, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 38)
- Audio Conference Program: Legal Foundation for the Zoning Ordinance, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 39)
- Audio Conference Program: Dealing with an Angry Public, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 40)
- ??? (Box 114, Folder 41)
- Audio Conference Program: Economic Development and Changing Communities, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 42)
- Audio Conference Program: Best Development Practices Part 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 43)
- Audio Conference Program: Best Development Practices Part 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 44)
- Audio Conference Program: Infill Development and the Redesign of Suburban Centers, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 45)
- Audio Conference Program: Urban Parks and Green Space Part 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 46)
- Audio Conference Program: Urban Parks and Green Space Part 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 47)
- Audio Conference Program: Shaping American Communities: Three Influential Books on City Planning, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Audio Conference Program: Livable Communities and Sustainable Development, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 2-3)
- Audio Conference Program: Transfer of Development Rights Revisited, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Audio Conference Program: Land Use Regulations and the Freedom of Expression, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Affordable Housing, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Farmland Preservation, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Public Anger and Community Decision-making, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Property Rights v. Public Resources Protection, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Best of Contemporary Community Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Audio/Web Conference Series, 2007-2008 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Audio Conference Series: Paying for Growth; Getting to Density, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Audio Conference Series: Mastering Meeting Management; Update on Planning and Enviromental Law; Planning Physically Active Communities, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Audio/Web Conference Training Series, 2008-2009; 2005-2006 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Regulating Religious Land Use, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 15)
- Preserving and Promoting Community Character, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Audio Conference Series: Teardowns, Monster Homes, and Appropriate Infill, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Audio Conference Series: Economic Development for Small Towns, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 18)
- Audio/Web Conference Training Series: Green Communities; Complete Streets; Inclusionary Housing; Planning Law Review; Universal Design; Maintaining Neighborhood Character. Introduction to the Planning Commission: Parts I and II. Introduction to the Zoning Board of Adjustment., 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 19)
- Audio Conference Training Series: Appointed and Elected Official Series. Context Specific Street Design; Green Infrastructure; Zoning Clinic; Suburban Place Making., 2003-2004 (Box 115, Folder 20)
- Audio Conference Training Series: AICP Training Practicing Planners Series, 2003-2004 (Box 115, Folder 21)
- CD-Rom Training: New Urbanist Codes, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 22)
- APA: Resources Nwesletter, 1990-2000 (Box 115, Folder 23-24)
- AICP Continuing Education Program, 1990-2000 (Box 115, Folder 25)
- APA/AICP: Education Program and Research Development. Teaching Adults; Guidelines for Developing a Chapter Education Plan., 1993 (Box 115, Folder 26)
- ASCP: Professional Guide and Administrative Guidelines. The Private Practice of Planning., 1992 (Box 115, Folder 27)
- Survey of Texas Planning Commissioners; How to Run a One-Hour Committee Meeting, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 28)
- APA-Council Programs Department-New Chapter Manuals, 1988-1992 (Box 115, Folder 29)
- Designing Leadership Training: Building Volunteer Effectiveness, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- APA/AICP Manual, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 2-3)
- AICP Professional Development Officer Manual, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 4-5)
- APA/AICP Staff Training Manual, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 6-7)
- APA Board of Directors Orientation Reference Manual, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 8-9)
- AICP Planners Training Service: Land Use Law for Planners and Lawyers (Box 116, Folder 10-12)
- The Management Idea Book, Paul Z. Zucker, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- AICP Planners Training Serice: Linking Land Use and Transportation, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 14-17)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 18)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 19)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 20)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 21)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 22)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey Data Tables, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey Appendix, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 5-7)
- APA National Planning Conference Attendees Survey, 2008 (Box 117, Folder 8-10)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 11-13)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 14-15)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 16-17)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 18-19)
- APA Board of Directors Business Meeting, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 20-21)
- APA Board/AICP Commission Orientation Manual, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 22-24)
- APA Executive Correspondence - Monthly Memos, 1994-1999 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Executive Director's Memo to APA Board/AICP Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- APA Elections, 1985-1988 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- APA Elections, 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- APA Elections, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- APA Elections, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- APA Elections, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 7-9)
- APA/AICP Elections, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 10)
- APA/AICP Elections, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 11-12)
- Teller Committee Election, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 13-14)
- APA Election Petition Candidates - Paperwork, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 15)
- APA Election Process and Information, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 16)
- APA/AICP Election Ballot Counts, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 17)
- APA/AICP Election Policies and Procedures, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 18)
- APA/AICP Elections Intelliscan, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 19)
- APA/AICP Election Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 20)
- APA/AICP Election Brochures, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 21)
- APA/AICP Elections Consolidated Component Questionnaire, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 22)
- APA/AICP Election- Intelliscan Online Version of Ballot, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 23)
- APA/AICP Election E-mail Blast Sample, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 24)
- APA/AICP Elections - Miscellaneous, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 25-26)
- "Zoning and all That Jazz:" 8th Annual Zoning Institute, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
- AICP 12th Annual Zoning Institute, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 3-6)
- Scenic America: Sign Control News, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- AICP Leadership Development for Experienced Planners, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- AICP 7th Annual Zoning Institute, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 9-12)
- AICP 9th Annual Zoning Institute, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 13-14)
- APiCP 1st Annual Zoning Institute, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 15)
- AICP 2nd Annual Zoning Institute, 1982 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- AICP 3rd Annual Zoning Institute, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 17)
- AICP 4th Annual Zoning Institute, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 18)
- AICP Sixth Annual Zoning Institute, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 19)
- AICP 7th Annual Zoning Institute, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 20)
- AICP 11th Annual Zoning Institute, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 21)
- AICP Neotraditional Town Planning, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 22-23)
- AICP Impact Fees: Paying for Growth, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 24-26)
- AICP Land Use Law for Planners and Lawyers, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 27-28)
- AICP Miscellaneous Workshops, 1987-1989 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- APA Elections, 2008 (Box 120, Folder 2-3)
- APA Election - Teller Committee, 2008 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- APA Election Labels, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- APA Election Ballots - Intelliscan, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- APA Board/AICP Commission Members, 1979-2005 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- APA/AICP Ad Hoc Committee on State Certification, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- AICP Licensing and Registration Miscellanous, 1989-1994 (Box 120, Folder 9-11)
- APA Liscensing- New Jersey, Florida, 1966-1992 (Box 120, Folder 12)
- APA Issues Telecommunication, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 13)
- APA v. University of Chicago Legal Documents, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 14-15)
- APA - Dolan v. City of Tigard, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 16)
- APA Issues - Takings, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 17)
- AICP Comission Miscellaneous, 1986-1994 (Box 120, Folder 18)
- APA/AICP Registered Trade Marks, 1988-1998 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- APA Planning Commissioner Task Force Report and Recommendations, 1992-1994 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- APA Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1985-1986 (Box 120, Folder 21)
- APA Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 22)
- APA Board of Directors Agendas, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 23)
- APA Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 24)
- APA Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 25)
- APA Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 27-29)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 1-3)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 4-7)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 8-14)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 15-21)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 22-26)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 27-29)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 30)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 1-6)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 7-12)
- APA/AICP Unknown Miscellaneous Materials (Box 122, Folder 13)
- APA Leadership Letter, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 14-16)
- APA Leadership Letter, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 17-21)
- APA Board: Travel Budget (San Francisco, 1994 and Portland, 1994) (Box 122, Folder 22)
- APA Finance - Next Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 23)
- APA Finance - Marketing, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 24)
- APA Finance - Investments, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 25)
- APA Finance - Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 26)
- APA Finance - Ratios/Other Financial Analysis, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 27)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 28)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 29)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 30)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 31)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 32)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 33)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 34)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 35)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 36)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 37)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 38)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 39)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 40)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 41)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 42)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 43)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1979 (Box 122, Folder 44)
- APA Strategic Plan, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- APA Strategic Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- APA Development Plan Budget, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- APA Development Plan, 1982-1986 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- APA Development and Strategic Plan, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- APA Development Plan, 1989-1993 (Box 123, Folder 6-8)
- APA/AICP Development Plan, 1991-1995 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- APA Strategic Plan, 1995-1998 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- Development Plans - Plans of Other Organizations, 1982-2000 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- APA Board Committee - Budget Data and Committee Information, 1995-1997 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- APA Board Committee - Executive, 1989-1994 (Box 123, Folder 13)
- APA Board Committee - Amicus Curiae, 1994-1997 (Box 123, Folder 14-15)
- APA Board Committee - Awards, 1994-1996 (Box 123, Folder 16)
- APA Development Plan and Budget Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 123, Folder 17-18)
- APA Board Committees - Ethical Awareness Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 123, Folder 19)
- APA Board Committees - Governance, Model State Enabling Legislation, National and State Policy Formation, 1994-1995 (Box 123, Folder 20)
- APA Board Committees - Membership, Undated (Box 123, Folder 21)
- APA Board Committees - Planning Support Task Force, 1977-1993 (Box 123, Folder 22-23)
- APA Board/Committees - Planning Officials Task Force, 1992-1994 (Box 123, Folder 24-25)
- APA Board and Committees - Task Force on Women and Minorities, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 26)
- APA Programs - Sponsored Research, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 27)
- APA Programs - Growing Smart, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 28)
- APA Programs - Growing Smart, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- APA Programs - Growing Smart, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- APA Programs - Planning Advisory Service, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- APA Programs - Planning Magazine, 1981-1986 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- APA - Teleconferencing Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- APA - Amicus Curiae Task Force Report 1 of 3, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- APA - Amicus Curiae Task Force Report 2 of 3, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- APA - Amicus Curiae Task Force Report 3 of 3, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 8)
- APA Chapter Newsletters
  - Alabama, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Alaska, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Arkansas, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - California - CAL Planner Coastal Connection, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - California - The Dispatch, The Memo, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - California - Northern News, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - California - The Orange County Planner, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - California - San Diego Planning Journal, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Colorado - Planning Matters, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Delaware, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Florida, 2003 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Florida 1 of 2, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Florida 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - APA Chapters Newsletters - Georgia, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Hawaii, 1998-2004 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Illionois, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Indiana 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Indiana 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Iowa, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - Kansas, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Kentucky, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Louisiana, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Maryland, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Michigan, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Missouri, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Washington, D.C., 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Nebraska, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Nevada, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - New England, 2003-2005 (Box 125, Folder 12-13)
  - New Jersey, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - New Mexico, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - New York Metro, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - New York Upstate, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - North Carolina, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 18-19)
  - Northern New England, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Ohio, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Oklahoma, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Oregon, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 23-24)
  - Pennsylvania, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 25-26)
  - Rhode Island, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - South Carolina, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Tennessee, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - Texas, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 30)
  - Utah, 2003-2005 (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - Virginia, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 32)
  - Washington, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Western Central, 2003-2005 (Box 125, Folder 34)
  - Western Planner, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
  - Wisconsin, 2002-2004 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 5)